(Sheldon:)We've already established
I'm found in the periodic table.
(Penny:)Well, it's a table, right?
(Penny:)I mean, why can't there
be food on it?
(Sheldon:)I knew she wasn't
lead car materiel.
(Penny:)Who elected you
Road Trip God?
(Penny:)Leonard.
(Leonard:)It was a late-night vote.
(Leonard:)We were all exhausted,
(Leonard:)and he was threatening
to filibuster.
(Leonard:)It's not technically
"Road Trip God""
(Leonard:)it's Travel Supervisor.
(Sheldon:)Although Road Trip God
does have a certain ring to it.
(Penny:)I don't understand
why you people
(Penny:)just let him bully
you like this.
(Penny:)Someone should
stand up to him.
(Penny:)What's he going to do?
(Penny:)I can't believe you let him
kick me out of the car.
(Howard:)What could we do?
He's the Travel Supervisor.
(Amy:)Don't worry, Penny.
This is a better car anyway.
(Howard:)Yeah. It's the Love Car.
(Penny:)Should I ask?
♪ They say we're young
and we don't know ♪
♪ We won't find out
until we grow ♪